Seven years later,
in 1888,
Jack the Ripper stalked
the streets of London,
murdering women in the night and holding
the entire city in his thrall. However,
he was nothing compared to
the horror that the feud
between JoJo and D would
unleash upon the world.
Let's go.
Hopeful.
For the way we will go.
Let the star across the world.
The force of the world will
be. Hopeful. Get on me.
Like the lying.
Notice that I'm burning.
In the night.
Interception!
The ball is plucked out
of the air by our hero,
Jonathan Joestar!
Joestar, a gentle giant
at 195 centimeters,
sprint for the tri-zone
with a spirited roar!
Can he win this?
The last game of his university career!
He's tackled from behind!
Wait!
He's still standing tall!
Two more fly in!
It's three on one out there!
Incredible!
He's still making for the try line,
undaunted by the men who dog his steps!
What power! What determination!
He's Hercules reborn!
Another tackle!
Oh, the weight's too much for him!
He flings it away and...
Yes!
There's the catch!
The ball lands safe in
the hands of Diobrando!
It's still anyone's game!
Can he make it?
He dodges one, and another!
He's done it!
There's nothing left between Dio and the
try line, and still he gives it his all!
Yes!
They did it!
On the last play, they snatched
victory out of the doors of defeat!
What teamwork!
When Jojo and Dio work together,
there's nothing they can't do!
Hell of a pass, Jojo.
All for naught if you hadn't
run it in like you did.
Watching you drag those defenders,
I couldn't just let you down.
Having finished his studies, Dio is
set to graduate with top marks in law.
Jojo, meanwhile, has set the faculty
afire with his bold thesis on archaeology.
On and off the field, these
two young men are giants.
They're the pride of our school.
Jojo, I think we should tell our father
about this victory of ours at once.
It's been seven years now since my
father welcomed Dio into our home.
Seven long years.
I smile and treat him as a brother.
But in my heart, nothing can
be further from the truth.
He's nothing if not affable.
And smart as a whip.
But I just can't forgive him
for his early villainies?
Dio, might you give us a quote
about your friendship with Jojo?
You seem quite close.
Right about the team, all of us!
Come on, tell us how close you are?
Hmm, should I?
Friendship, huh?
The truth is, I despise
this grinning imbecile.
I've spent seven years making
nice to that Joestar brat.
But now that I am of age!
I shall bring my plans to fruition.
At long last, the Joestar
fortune will be mine!
And devil take anyone
who tries to stop me?
Father, how are you feeling today?
But for this cough, much
improved over yesterday?
The doctors say I should
be in the hospital! Why?
I fear it would do you no good
Hospitals only care about profit.
They'd measure you for a
shroud ere they saw you cured.
Then here I shall remain.
The comforts of home are
curative like as not.
My chest doesn't pain me so.
And the swelling has gone down.
I'm on the mend.
It was just a cold.
Why has it worsened so?
I heard tell of your victory.
Stunning bit of teamwork.
Someone told you about it?
I got word straight away
from an old college chum.
Whoever he is, he's fast.
I'm glad he wasn't on our opponent's
team or we could have lost.
I'm proud of you, lads.
You both turned out so well.
Providence is too kind.
Dio, I'm so glad you've thrived.
Pursue your ambitions,
whatever they may be.
I will lend you aid in
any way I can, my son.
You rescued me from calamity.
Already my debt is more
than I can ever repay.
You do me too much honor.
The secret is mine alone.
I can't imagine for what purpose this
mask may have been fashioned, or by whom.
But it belonged to my mother, and
so having it near is a comfort,
strange as that may seem.
When I finally outwit
the sphinx of a mask,
it will be the talk of
the archaeological world.
My goodness!
Many thanks to you, Master Dio.
Hmm.
The years betray me.
Climbing the stairs is much
harder than it was before.
This letter!
Having read it, all has been made clear!
Dio!
I think he's...
Wait, that's...
That's father's medicine.
He's due for his next dosage.
All this time, you're the one
who's been bringing it to him.
Yes, what of it?
This letter.
Your father sent it to mine.
Guess what it says.
Your lordship, sickness
has laid me right low.
It's the end of me, whatever it is.
My chest hurts,
my fingers are all swollen up, and I
can't breathe but for all this coughing.
Those are the same symptoms as father's.
Blow for blow.
No way is this mere coincidence.
Dio!
What are you trying to say, Jojo?
I'm having a doctor look at this powder.
Jojo, if you think I would poison father,
then from this day forward,
you and I are friends no more.
Try as I might, I can't
look Dio in the eye.
It's because I lack proof.
All I have to go on are my suspicions.
Now then, if you put that
medicine back on the tray,
I'll be willing to forget
about your lapse in judgment.
Dio, there's only one way
you're going to convince me.
Swear to me that the
contents of this are safe.
Do it in Dario's name.
Swear to me on Dario's
honor as a gentleman.
Do that and I'll never
bring up this moment again.
If my hunch proves true,
his father's honor is the one lie
that will catch in his throat.
Say it!
What are you waiting for?
I... swear...
How can I swear on the honor
of a man who didn't have any?
He deserved to die!
How's that for the truth, Jojo?
You just gave me all
the proof I needed, Dio.
At hearing his name, you lashed out.
I don't know what he could have done
that moved you to such murderous rage,
but murder him you surely did!
You hurt father never again, Dio!
Damn your eyes.
Of course.
You've been planning to
murder him for years now.
I knew it.
I knew that you were playing Foss with us.
But now your villainy is over.
Once I've learned what this is, I'm
taking it to the police straight away.
Damn it.
Their fortune was within my grasp.
Was it fate that Jojo
found out when he did?
No.
No, it was that letter.
He vexes me, even now!
You're weak, just like your mother!
He drove her to an early grave.
Knowing that curse blood flows through
my veins, it's enough to drive me mad!
Ser Joestar lives, for now.
I'll be back from London
in a few days, Father.
Till then, accept medicine only from the
hands of these doctors and no one else.
Master Jojo said he doesn't
want me to bring it up? Yes.
We will do as Jojo has instructed us.
His reasons are a mystery to me,
but I trust the boy with my life.
Thank you, Father.
However, his illness is getting worse.
If it is a poison, he
may need an antidote.
Whatever you may learn in
London about the poison,
I'll see you take the
truth of it to your grave.
Your death will be the perfect crime.
Seven years ago, this
mask reacted to my blood.
The spikes hidden within will
make short work of Jojo's brain.
His injuries will be so unique, there'll
be nothing at all to tie it back to me.
Jojo, your curiosity will
lead to your destruction.
The university couldn't identify
this so-called medicine,
though they did speculate that it
was a compound from the Orient.
Therefore...
Young Master, that stretch
of road there is Ogre Street,
the most dangerous
alleyway in all of London.
Yes, I know.
But this is the one place I will
be able to find what I came for.
You're more than welcome to leave.
Dio grew up in London.
Where else in England could
he have acquired such a toxin?
I shall have my evidence
and Father's Antidote.
Another dead end.
That cat, it was eating a puppy.
You do the honors, Tattoo. Right!
Use that shiv of yours to slice him open.
I want his guts for garters.
Ogre street, it is aptly named.
Check out this idiot!
He grabbed my blade!
In all my days, I've never seen the like!
Stuck, ain't ya?
One quick yank of the
knife and I'll be picking
your fingers out of the
snow for a fortnight.
Try it, then.
The moment you pull,
my foot will kick out at your groin
with all the force of a sledgehammer.
I'm willing to see our
transaction through.
Are you, Zero?
I'm fighting to protect my family
from those who wish it harm.
I doubt very much that your
resolve is equal to mine.
That's quite enough.
Now tell me, one of you, where can I
find an Asian apothecary? Tough talk.
If you're looking to lose
body parts, do stick around.
Observe.
I'll mince you right finally,
with the tip of the hat.
And now we dance.
I have to find that
apothecary, no matter the cost.
Don't tell me this here's
your first proper dust-up.
If you mean to block like that,
it'll be your last one too.
Ha-ha!
Cut you straight to the bone, looks like.
Granted, I didn't think you'd
hooved the shiv at me like that,
but my Cheap still hit its mark.
Now I know why he weren't
defending himself better.
Fingers, hands, legs.
He don't care one whit what he loses.
It's as if his resolve runs
deeper than pain or fear.
I took the lad for an easy mark.
I guess I've been right
disabused of that notion.
What?
JoJo went to Ogre Street on his own?
I told him it was perilous.
Keep this to yourself.
Sir Joestar is still unwell.
Yes, sir.
I guess I won't need to
use the mask after all.
There, alone, his fate is sealed.
That's enough, lads.
I won't let a single one of you lay
a finger on that gentleman there.
But why?
Tell me something.
Strong as a bull you
are, it's plain to see.
You could have stove my head
in with that foot of yours,
but you went easy on me, didn't you?
I came here for the sake of my father.
You have a family.
People who expect you to
return from this dark business?
It is not my place to cause them grief.
He means it, don't he?
How this Fool survived so long?
Wait
He spared my mate's lives
just like he did mine!
I like the cut of his jib.
Sure he's naive, but he's a gentleman
through and through this one.
I want to know the name
of him who spared me.
Jonathan Joestar.
Well, pleased to make your acquaintance.
If it's Asian concoctions you're
looking for, mind your back.
The druggist is one sly customer.
So Joestar, Jojo's been gone three days.
Whatever his errand, he'll accomplish it.
Where have the years gone, I wonder?
He's grown into a fine man.
I cannot help but wonder if I was
too hard on the boy growing up.
I'm sure Jojo's laying
dead in some alley by now.
Did he find the apothecary?
Look at me, swilling it down.
Nothing but a drunken fool, just
like my bastard father, damn it!
Watch yourself, or have you no
respect for your elders, boy?
Look at the baby, tolling
round past bedtime,
sucking on a bottle like
it was his mother's tea.
Look at the man when he's talking,
didn't your old man teach you right?
Oh my god, just for that, I'm
gonna take your face clean off ya!
Oh, your threat has me quaking
in my boots, you old guttersnipe.
How will I escape this
moment of mortal peril?
How about we use this?
It's meant for Jojo, but
you'll make a fine guinea pig.
Just die already!
Yeah, yeah, let's see what you can do?
That light
All of that spectacle, for nothing.
Useless.
That was boring.
I expected more from you, Mask.
Impossible.
He's alive!
That face!
Those teeth!
No!
What incredible strength!
Even now he advances, but his
hand, does the pain mean nothing?
He shattered my shoulder
with but a glancing blow.
The river, I must jump in.
It's odd.
I was drinking through the night, but
suddenly I got such a brutal thirst.
My blood!
It's draining it!
What the...
So this is the secret of the mask.
I'm dying.
No!
I had such plans!
Must my last sight on Earth
be this damnable sunrise?
The sun destroyed him.
What's the meaning of this?
Why is it so bloody dark?
Jojo.
You're a poisoner, Dio Brando.
I have all the proof I
require, and then some.
I'll be the roundabout.
The words will make you out and out.
I'll spend the day your way.
Call it morning driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
The music dance and sing.
They make the children really ring.
I spend the day your way.
Cold in morning driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
Then out around the lake.
Now let's come out of the sky.
And they'll stand there.
When my lover will be there.
And we'll see you.
Ten true summers.
We'll be there.
Laughing too.
Twenty-four and five.
My lover will see.
I'll be there with you.
Jojo, I've been a devil,
but grant me this one wish.
This fellow reeks of brimstone and blood!
You see, I am about to
become so much more! Dio!